Hot Stuff
Sittin' here eatin' my heart out waitin' waiting for some lover to call
Dialed about a thousand numbers lately
Almost rang the phone off the wall
Lookin' for some hot stuff baby this evenin'
I need some hot stuff baby tonight
I want some hot stuff baby this evenin'
Gotta have some hot stuff
Gotta have some love tonight
I need hot stuff
I want some hot stuff
Lookin' for a lover who needs another
Don't want another night on my own
Wanna share my love with a warm blooded lover
Wanna bring a wild man back home
Gotta have some hot love baby this evening
I need some hot stuff baby tonight
I want some hot stuff baby this evening
Gotta have some lovin'
Got to have love tonight
I need hot stuff hot love lookin' for hot love
How's about some hot stuff baby this evenin'
I need some hot stuff baby tonight
Gimme little hot stuff baby this evenin'
Hot stuff baby gonna need your love tonight
I need hot love lookin' for hot love wanna have hot love
Sittin' here eating my heart, no reason
Won't spend another night on my own
I dialed about a hundred numbers lately
I'm bound to find somebody home
Gonna have some hot stuff baby this evenin'
I need some hot stuff baby tonight
Looking for my hot stuff baby this evenin'
Need some loving baby
Gonna need your love tonight
Hot stuff baby this evening
I need some hot stuff baby tonight, yeah yeah
I want some hot stuff baby this evenin'
I want some hot stuff baby tonight
Yeah hey hey hey now hot love, baby
I need your hot stuff baby tonight
I want your hot stuff baby this evenin'
Hot stuff baby
Gonna need your love tonight